Pouya **Aghahoseini**

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT · AMIRKABIR UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

No.16, Tavakol Alley, 17-Shahrivar Ave, Tehran, 1153963716, Iran

🛮 (+98) 9102117201 | 🚾 pouyaaghahoseini@gmail.com | 🌴 pouyaaghahoseini.github.io | 🖸 pouyaaghahoseini | 🛅 pouyaaghahoseini

Summary_

Currently studying Computer Science at Amirkabir University of Technology. During my recent years in Amirkabir, I have had the opportunity to gain lots of teamwork experiences, through course projects and more significantly, through extracurricular activities in student scientific chapter. I am generally interested in Business Intelligence, Software Development, and Data Science.

Skills

Programming C/C++, Python, R, MATLAB

Web Technologies HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL

Libraries numPy, Pandas

Operating Systems Linux, Windows

Languages Persian, English(Proficient)

Miscellaneous MTFX, Jupyter, Git, Microsoft Office, GAMS(Optimization), Database Design

Education

Amirkabir University of Technology

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

• Major in Computer Science, CGPA: 17.28/20

Allameh Helli High School

DIPLOMA IN MATHEMATICS AND PHYSICS

• Grade: 18.5/20

Tehran, Iran

2016 - Present

Tehran, Iran

2012 - 2016

Experience

Math & Computer Science Faculty, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran Sep 2018 - Present

TEACHING ASSISTANT

• Design and Analysis of Algorithms - Instructor: Dr.MohammadReza Kazemi

- Data Structures and Algorithms Instructor: Dr.Mohammad Akbari
- Fundamentals of Programming: C Language Instructor: Dr.Farzaneh Salari
- Compilers Instructor: Dr.Mohammad Hassan Shirali-Shahreza
- Introduction to the Theory of Computation Instructor: Dr.Fatemeh Zare-Mirakabad

Student Scientific Chapter, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran

HEAD OF INFORMATICS AND COMPETITIONS

Mar. 2018 - Mar. 2019

- Organized Data Science Seminars And Workshops.
- Coordinated 5 ACM Contests.
- Arranged On-Site Visits To Leading Tech Companies In Tehran.
- Arranged Talks With Alumni Currently Studying Or Working Abroad.
- Held 2018 New Student Orientation Program.
- Organized And Instructed Exam Preparation Classes(Calculus, Programming, Differential Equations).

11th Winter School on Computational Geometry, Amirkabir University of Technology

Tehran, Iran

ORGANIZING COMMITTEE MEMBER

March 2019

- The Winter School on Computational Geometry is held every year by Math and Computer Science Faculty, in collaboration with IPM Institute for Research in Fundamental Sciences.
- Notable researchers in computational geometry are invited for seminars and workshops in this program.

Projects

Medify: An Application for Fixing Tags And Organizing Media Files

Amirkabir University of Technology

Software Design Course | 4 member team | 🧿 Github

Jan. 2018 - Jul. 2018

- The application was Developed using ${\bf Scrum\ Methodology}$ for Agile Software Development.
- We did 5 presentations throughout including a 5-minute startup pitch presentation and the presentation of the first MVP

FEBRUARY 16, 2020 POUYA AGHAHOSEINI · RÉSUMÉ

Designing and Creating A Database From YAGO Datasets

DATABASE COURSE PROJECT ☐ GITHUB

- Data Extraction using TSV files acquired from max plank institute website.
- Processing and Clustering TSV files with Python and MySQL.
- Designing and Creating A 3NF Database.

Factory Simulation with MATLAB

SIMULATION PROJECT O GITHUB

- System modeling and simulation with MATLAB
- Simulation of a factory with different performances and various response time of each agent.

Amirkabir University of Technology

Jan. 2018 - Jul. 2018

Amirkabir University of Technology

Sep. 2018 - Jan. 2019